



jesusmarzor.com



/jesusmarzor



/jesusmarzor



jesusmarzor28@gmail.com

Lenguages

Javacript Java
PHP Python
SQL C++

Technologies

React Git

Next.js Docker Laravel Linux MySQL SCRUM

Jesús Martín

Front-end Developer

Profile

I'm Jesús Martín Zorrilla, I'm studing Computer Engineering. I've studied web developer since 2021. I programme almost every day because it's one of my favorite hobbies.

I propose myself new objectives every day in order to continue learning and trying to use new technologies.

Experiences

february 2022 - Currently | Secrets-On, Madrid

React Front-end Developer

Responsabilities:

- Cooperate with the development of the website in wordpress.
- Cooperate with the development of the plataform.

Recommendations that I've contributed:

- Work with a methodology agile.
- Use SASS and Suit CSS together.
- A folder structure more sustainable.

Stack: Wordpress, SASS, Suit CSS, Javascript, React, Docker.

Distinguished project

february 2022 - june 2022 | Final Degree Project

Web application for restaurant business

My objetive is speed up this sector so I've created a web application for that the clients will be able to reserve table, order and pay without contact with the waiter.

Stack: Tailwind, Javascript, React, Nextjs, PHP, MySQL, Laravel.

Education

Degree in Computer Engineering - University of Granada september 2017 - Currently

Cybersecurity course - HTL escuela de empresa online *february 2022 - august 2022*

Idiomas

Spanish | Native English | Basic